Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pete Seeger records songs with 1199 members, 9/1977 (Box 64, Folder 97)
  #2519
- Marge Naughton + dog, 9/1977 (Box 64, Folder 98)
  #2520
- Full Employment Rally, Sept. 1977 (Box 64, Folder 99)
  #2521
- French Unionist, Sept. 1977 (Box 64, Folder 100)
  #2522
- Joint Delegate Assem., Sept. 6, 1977 - Belafonte, Seeger, Sept. 1977 (Box 64, Folder 101)
  #2523
- St. Mary's grievance, 9/15/1977 (Box 64, Folder 102)
  #2524
- Boat ride, Aug. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  #2525
- Mass. Delegates Conference, 9/17/1977 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  #2526
- Ted Mitchell Retirement, 9/16/1977 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  #2527
- Philly negotiations + Temple + Wills Eye Strike, July 1977 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  #2528
- Cahell, Huntington workers rally + meet - Doris gets key to city, 9/1977 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  #2532
- Doctors Memorial Hospital Welch, W. Va. workers meet, 9/1977 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  #2530
- X-ray Comm. Mtg., 9/1977 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  #2531
- Delegate weekend - Queens, L.I., 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Carol Bellomy - Spouse abuse meeting, 10/4/1977 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  #2533
- Lab Committee, 10/6/1977 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  #2534
- Lamont Patterson, 10/5/1977 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  #2535
- Cabell Huntington Hosp. Strike, W. Va., 10/7-8/1977 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  #2536a
- Cabell Huntington Hosp. Strike, W. Va., 10/7-8/1977 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  #2536b
- Calendar - with Maggie Zaphire, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  #2537
- Eleanor Jackson, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  #2538
- RN Division, 10/12/1977 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  #2539
- Nat'l. Exec. Bd., 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  #2540
- Marshall Garcia, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  #2541 -- EMPTY
- United Hospital 1199J Guild Delegate, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  #2542
- Hand family of Southampton Hospital, 10/27/1977 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  #2543
- Camp Committee, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  #2544
- W. Va. Striker Madelyn Moore, Oct. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  #2545
- Queens - L.I. joint delegate assembly (Box 65, Folder 23)
  #2546
- Eleven 99 Plaza Health Center, Oct. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  #2547
- Mt. Sinai bio medical electronic Tech. Change, Oct. 1977 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  #2548
- Lisa Silverberg, 11/1/1977 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  #2549
- Delores LeVaul, 10/31/1977 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  #2550
- People-Joan Manners, 11/1/1977 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  #2551
- Organizers Institute at Pawking, 11/8/1977 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  #2553
- RN Delegate Assembly, 11/9/1977 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  #2554
- Drug Membership meeting, 11/9/1977 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  #2555 -- EMPTY
- Rhode Island delegate conference, 10/29/1977 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  #2556
- Delegates (Manhattan) at Pawling, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  #2557 -- EMPTY
- Penn. Prof. Conf. in Hershey, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  #2558
- Hazel Jones, 10/1977 (Box 65, Folder 35)
  #2559
- Proxy Nesbitt, Nov. Hosp. Div. Del. Assem., 11/1977 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  #2560
- People - Vicki Carlton-Wilde, 11/30/1977 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  #2561
- St. John's RNs, 12/1/1977 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  #2562
- 1959 Strike pix of Dubin - w/'Reinstate Turner' signs (Box 65, Folder 39)
  #2563 -- 1 photograph
- Beth Israel delegates, 1/10/1978 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  #2564 -- EMPTY
- Heartland of Charleston, W. Va., 1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  #2565
- Roger Wilkins at Guild Assembly, 1/13/1978 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  #2566
- St. Mary Hosp., Gary, Indiana, 1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 43)
  #2567
- Guild delegates 1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 44)
  #2568
- LPN Committee, 1/20/1978 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  #2569
- Grant task force, 1/30/1978 (Box 65, Folder 46)
  #2570
- Joint Diseases, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 47)
  #2571
- Columbia Computer Center, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 48)
  #2572
- Span. Affairs Comm. Dance, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 49)
  #2573
- Training Fund meeting, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 50)
  #2574
- Marion Smith injured at Joint Diseases, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 51)
  #2575
- RN delegate training class, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 52)
  #2576
- Retirees - Spanish + black history, 3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 53)
  #2577
- Philly Deleg. Banquet, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 54)
  #2578
- Pharm. Committee, 2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 55)
  #2579
- Cabell Pickets, 2/16/1978 (Box 65, Folder 56)
  #2580 -- EMPTY
- Radiology delegates, 3/1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 57)
  #2581
- LPN Committee, 3/2/1978 (Box 65, Folder 58)
  #2582
- Guild delegate Class, 3/1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 59)
  #2583
- Lab Safety Comm., 3/1/1978 (Box 65, Folder 60)
  #2584
- M.L. King Center, 3/7/1978 (Box 65, Folder 61)
  #2585
- Handshake, 3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 62)
  #2586
- St. John's Episcopal Pharmacists, 3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 63)
  #2587
- Albany lobby, 3/22/1978 (Box 65, Folder 64)
  #2588
- Labor Law (Milwaukee), 3/27/1978 (Box 65, Folder 65)
- Bx-Leb Community Fight, 3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 66)
  #2590
- Bx-Kidney Ratification, 4/3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 67)
  #2591
- Mary Heye, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 68)
  #2592
- Guild delegates, 4/13/1978 (Box 65, Folder 69)
  #2593
- RN Alcoholic Conference, 4/15/1978 (Box 65, Folder 70)
  #2594
- Spanish Affairs Committee (Box 65, Folder 71)
  #2595
- Koni Cernohs, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 72)
  #2596
- Post Demo, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 73)
  #2597
- Dieticians Study Group, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 74)
  #2598
- Nena Strike, 4/14/1978 (Box 65, Folder 75)
  #2599
- LIJ Blood Program, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 76)
  #2600
- Russian visitors, 4/19/1978 (Box 65, Folder 77)
  #2601
- Legal Aid, 4/25/1978 (Box 65, Folder 78)
  #2602
- Pawling Weekend, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 79)
  #2603
- Pathmark Warehouse Strike, 4/1978 (Box 65, Folder 80)
  #2604
- NENA Strike, 4/21/1978 (Box 65, Folder 81)
  #2605
- Legal Aid, 4/25/1978 (Box 65, Folder 82)
  #2606
- B'klynn Jewish, 5/3/1978 (Box 65, Folder 83)
  #2607
- Pawling, 5/6/1978 (Box 65, Folder 84)
  #2608
- Gloria Arana on the job two month before retirement (Box 65, Folder 85)
  #2609
- Blood Conference, 5/12/1978 (Box 65, Folder 86)
  #2610
- League Negs., May, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 87)
  #2611
- Stan St. Jeur retirement party, May 1978 (Box 65, Folder 88)
  #2612
- CAT Scanner, May 1978 (Box 65, Folder 89)
  #2613
- Afr. Trade Union Women, May 1978 (Box 65, Folder 90)
  #2614
- Gary delegates training, 5/1978 (Box 65, Folder 91)
  #2615
- RN Conference, 6/1978 (Box 65, Folder 92)
  #2616 -- EMPTY
- Kathy Obelson (Box 65, Folder 93)
  #2617
- Retirees banquet, 6/22/1978 (Box 65, Folder 94)
  #2618 -- EMPTY
- Davis + Biesel, 6/22/1978 (Box 65, Folder 95)
  #2619 -- EMPTY
- Davis - CBS, 7/1978 (Box 65, Folder 96)
  #7/1978 -- EMPTY
- JIGC Yiddish, May 1978 (Box 65, Folder 97)
  #2621
- Drug Delegs, Ismalun + Winderman + Ray Schustack, Apr. 1978 (Box 65, Folder 98)
  #2622
- Philly: 1199C - 1978 installation, May 1978 (Box 65, Folder 99)
  #2623
- Max Fine, Aug. 1978 (Box 65, Folder 100)
  #2624
- Queens Botanical Garden Puppet Show: retired members + their grandchildren (Box 65, Folder 101)
  #2625
- Columbia Pres. Guild members voting to ratify 1978 contract (Box 65, Folder 102)
  #2626
- Haven Manor: contract signed - July 1978 (Box 65, Folder 103)
  #2627
- Doug Fraser UAW w/Davis + Foner, July 1978 (Box 65, Folder 104)
  #2628
- Beth Israel Nurses affiliate RN's, Aug. 1978 (Box 65, Folder 105)
  #2629
- Gov. Carey at Flushing Hosp. kissed by Hosp. Division Delegate Frankie Amoruso, Aug. 4, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 106)
  #2630
- People Sandra Messina, Aug. 20, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 107)
  #2631
- PA Delegates, 8/1978 (Box 65, Folder 108)
  #2632
- Scherimer strike, 8/19/1978 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  #2633
- Berek Confirmation, July, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  #2634
- Sondra Clark; RNs Dis. Leader, Aug. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  #2635
- Lab Safety Seminar, Aug. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  #2636
- Bermuda Hospital Trade Unionists visit 1199, Aug. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  #2637
- Ritter, Brian, 9/6/1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  #2638
- LeGall, Lynn, 9/6/1978 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  #2639
- Schervies (St. Pat's), 9/6/1978 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  #2640
- Blood Bank L.I.J. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  #2641
- Flushing Hospital Med. Records grievance w/organizer Jeff Colzen, Aug. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  #2642
- Lab Safety: features Linda Johnson, delegate from L.I.J., July 1978 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  #2643
- Peggy Eason - Blind delegate at Jewish Guild for the blind, Sept. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  #2644
- Beeman Hosp. workers 2/new pay raise, 9/8/1978 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  #2645
- Connecticut organizing campaign: Davis speaks, Jerry Brown, etc., Aug. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  #2646
- Brian Ritter, Lynn LeGall, Sondra Clark: RN Organizers, Sept. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  #2647
- Logan Hospital Yard Sale with Doris, Talbert, Sept. 9, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  #2648
- Flushing clericals, 9/27/1978 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  #2650 -- EMPTY
- Davis wins the most, 9/1978 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  #2651
- Gramery Park (Box 66, Folder 19)
  #2652
- Arthur Ave. in Bronx (Box 66, Folder 20)
  #2653
- Pharmacists Education Class, Sept. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  #2654
- Training + Upgrading report: Features upgraded member Donnie Joynes, Rob Melendez, Evelyn Wiscobitch, Oct. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  #2655
- Hempstead Hosp. Members' Training Class, Sept. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  #2656
- Hempstead Hosp. Kitchen, 9/1978 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  #2657
- Albert Sica - heard N.Y.S., Pharmacy Board, 9/1978 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  #2658
- Amy Metroka, 9/1978 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  #2659
- Dr. T. Cahill at 1199 for Carey, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  #2660
- RN delegates being sworn in, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  #2661
- Legal Aid Society meeting - Dan Glickster presides, Oct. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  #2662
- Radiology Committee - slides on mammography, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  #2663
- Union Buster Certificate for Nancy Stiefel, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  #2664
- Ray Marshall at 1199C: Sec. of Labor, with Congressional Candidate Rev. Wm. Gray, 10/10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  #2665
- Irwin Friemark at black board - Pose for possible cover on Union Busters, 10/12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  #2666
- Columbia Pres. Radiology - Grievance Committee - won posting of radiology badge readings, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 34)
  #2667
- Thanksgiving women (Carmen Quinines, Katherine Cogan), Oct. 1978 (Box 66, Folder 35)
  #2668
- RN's + the Law Conference, 10/21/1978 (Box 66, Folder 36)
  #2669
- Connecticut Org. Campaign, 10/15/1978 (Box 66, Folder 37)
  #2670
- Retired members give gifts to children at Logan Hosp. (gifts made by Retirees), 10/27/1978 (Box 66, Folder 38)
  #2671
- Ede Marinoff, 10/25/1978 (Box 66, Folder 39)
  #2672
- Nat'l. Exec. Board + Organizers - Conference at Pawling, 10/25-29/1978 (Box 66, Folder 40)
  #2674
- Scholarship Coupon Photo - for Dec. Issue, 10/31/1978 (Box 66, Folder 41)
- Philadelphia Training + Upgrading People featured in Dec. issue, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 42)
  #2675
- Cancer care RN's story Dec. 1978 feature, 8/1978 (Box 66, Folder 43)
  #2676
- Bob Ward - w/Congressional Candidate, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 44)
  #2677
- Fairmont W. Va. Strike (Box 66, Folder 45)
  #2678
- Hospital Pharmacists Training Class - Graduation, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 46)
  #2679
- Marathon Runners from 1199, E. Schtab + V. Collett, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 47)
  #2680
- Albert Einstein strike, 10/1978 (Box 66, Folder 48)
  #2681
- Election Day leafletting for Carey, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 49)
  #2682
- Guild delegate training class, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 50)
  #2683
- Cancer Care Conference at 1199, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 51)
  #2684
- Pawling weekend for area organizers, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 52)
  #2685
- Beth Israel RN's - demonstrate fro more staffing, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 53)
  #2686
- Nyack Hospital, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 54)
  #2688 -- EMPTY
- Mid-Bergen Mental Health Center, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 55)
  #2689
- Joanna Miller, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 56)
  #2690
- Montefiore Pharmacists, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 57)
  #2691
- William F. Ryan, Health Center, Contacts, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 58)
  #2692a
- William F. Ryan Health Center, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 59)
  #2692b
- Davis sit in at St. Patrick's for Schervier, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 60)
  #2693
- Pennsylvania Professional Conference, 11/1978 (Box 66, Folder 61)
  #2694
- Christmas party for 1199 kids - What a horrendous affair - Bah Humbug, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 62)
  #2695a
- Kids Christmas Party, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 63)
  #2695b
- Ted Kennedy + Arlene Ezratty, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 64)
  #2696
- Postal workers demonstrate 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 65)
  #2697
- Logan Hospital improvements, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 66)
  #2698
- Retired members Christmas Party, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 67)
  #2699
- New Rochelle negotiation, 1/1978 (Box 66, Folder 68)
  #2700
- Guild delegate training, 1/1978 (Box 66, Folder 69)
  #2701
- Hospital Division Delegate Training Class graduates, 1/1978 (Box 66, Folder 70)
  #2702
- Bread + Roses: meeting with hospital administrators, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 71)
  #2703
- Max Bloom, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 72)
  #2704
- N.J. Mid-Bergen Sheltered workshop, Jan. 17, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 73)
  #2705
- Sown Seeds Gallery 1199 opening - UNICEF children's art, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 74)
  #2706a
- Sown Seeds Gallery 1199 opening - UNICEF children's art, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 75)
  #2706b
- Paul Davis + Moe w/Bread + Roses poster, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 76)
  #2707
- Morris Crowe, 12/1978 (Box 66, Folder 77)
  #2708
- Connecticut Professionals Organizing Committee, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 78)
  #2709
- Burt Silverman portrait of Leon Davis, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 79)
  #2710
- Coalition to save Brooklyn Jewish in Albany + at City Hall, 1/1979 (Box 66, Folder 80)
  #2711
- Brookdale ratification, 11/15/1978 (Box 66, Folder 81)
  #2712
- Carol Zimmerman: RN at Jamaica, 2/1979 (Box 66, Folder 82)
  #2713
- Guild delegates training class, 2/1979 (Box 66, Folder 83)
  #2714
- Nate Hackney, 2/1979 (Box 66, Folder 84)
  #2715
- Mitch Olinsky, 2/1979 (Box 66, Folder 85)
  #2716
- Dr. Daniel Faierman at meeting with Pharmacists + Dieticians, or Diabetics, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  #2717
- Riker's Island 1199 workers, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  #2718
- Member interviewed by Nat'l. Public Radio on Bread + Roses, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  #2719
- Joint Delegate Assembly w/Odetta, 2/6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  #2720
- Furriers Union Retirees visit Gallery 1199, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  #2721
- New Rochelle Negotiators, 1/1979 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  #2722
- Bread + Roses: Moe meets religion leaders 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  #2723
- Philly Nursing Home conference, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  #2724
- Fairmont ratification, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  #2725
- Eve Rheinhart, 2/1979 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  #2726
- Brooklyn Jewish 1199ers demonstrate in Albany, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  #2727
- Nassau County - Mental Health Workers Strike, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  #2728
- Moses Credit - Fashion Show at Mt. Sinai, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  #2729
- Long Island College Hosp. 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  #2730
- Einstein Comprehensive Family Care Center, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  #2731
- Waldbaum pickets, 3/1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  #2732
- Columbia U. Pickets, 4/1979 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  #2733
- Camp Selection Committee, March 1979 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  #2734
- Kingsbury HIP Strike, May 1979 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  #2735
- Muelenkamp's Southern Tour, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  #2736
- Scholarship Counseling, May 1979 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  #2737
- New Jersey Swearing in Ceremony, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  #2738
- Belafonte at 1199, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 23)
  #2739
- Long Island College Hospital: leaflet shots, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 24)
  #2740
- Philly - RN conference on 1985 proposal, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 25)
  #2741
- Fairmont, W. Va. delegate training, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  #2742
- Velia Toznelli: delegate Bird S. Coler Hosp., 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  #2743
- Edna Mallos: Flushing Hosp., 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  #2744
- Ray Dachinger, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  #2745
- Dieticians, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  #2746
- Credit Union - Save for 1980, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  #2747
- Mott Haven Day Care: Health Day, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  #2748
- Connecticut State Employees testify for raise: story in July 1979 issue, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  #2749
- Clotilda Thomas, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  #2750
- Oral History Group Shot, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 35)
  #2751
- 1199 P RN Conference, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  #2752
- Puerto Rican Travelling Theatre + Roy Brown :Bread + Roses Event, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  #2753
- Sherry Denend - Pharmacist at North Central Bronx, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  #2754
- Daughters of Jacob RN's victory, 5/1975 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  #2755
- Esther Rentas + Father + Son: Camp feature, 5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  #2756
- Ossie Davis + Stephanie Mills: B & R event, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  #2757
- Beth Israel ventilator grievance, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  #2758
- Futima Morales + Family, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  #2759
- Patient Care Conference planning Session a Bread + Roses event, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  #2760
- Swedish Trade Unionists visit 1199: ya, ya, Sven, 6/1975 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  #2761
- Howard Rokey Chorale: performs at 1199, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  #2762
- Georgeen Comerford, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  #2763
- Vassar Brothers Strike, 7/1979 (Box 67, Folder 48)
  #2764
- Long Island College Hospital: leafletting prior to election, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 49)
  #2765
- Labor Theatre: "I Just Wanted Someone to Know", 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 50)
  #2766
- East Side Org. Office, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 51)
  #2767
- Josef Mayer, 7/20/1979 (Box 67, Folder 52)
  #2768
- Sam Levinson, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 53)
  #2769
- Gary, Ind. Union Busters Conference, 6/1979 (Box 67, Folder 54)
  #2770
- Vassar Hospital Strikers, 7/31/1979 (Box 67, Folder 55)
  #2771
- 1199 P. delegate assembly, Aug. 6, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 56)
  #2773a
- 1199 P Delegate Assembly, Aug. 6, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 57)
  #2773b (cont.)
- Chambersburg, Pa. Strike, Aug. 6, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 58)
  #2775
- Retirees Banquet - June 1979, Aug. 6, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 59)
  #2776
- Rochel Weinstein, 8/1979 (Box 67, Folder 60)
  #2777
- Mort Stewart, 8/1979 (Box 67, Folder 61)
  #2779
- Bread + Roses filming in Hosp., July 1979 (Box 67, Folder 62)
  #2780
- RN Ed. Committee Meeting on Patient, July 1979 (Box 67, Folder 63)
  #2781
- Willhaven (Milwaukee) grievance, 8/1979 (Box 67, Folder 64)
  #2782
- New Guild Staff members, 9/1979 (Box 67, Folder 65)
  #2783
- Aribel Garcia, Wins reinstatement (Box 67, Folder 66)
  #2784
- Comm. Office open house, Sept. 1979 (Box 67, Folder 67)
  #2785
- Delegate weekend - Brooklyn, 9/1979 (Box 67, Folder 68)
  #2786
- Retired members near history project with Walden School, 10/5/1979 (Box 67, Folder 69)
  #2787
- Great Nurses meeting, 10/10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 70)
  #2788
- Estlerlyn Boas, 10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 71)
  #2789
- Birmingham, Ala. Organizing Mtg., 10/1979 (Box 67, Folder 72)
  #2790
- Pregnant Clerical Worker (10 ft.), Nov. 1, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  #2791
- Bronx Lebanon Rally, Sept. 1979, Sept. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  #2792
- RN Conference on 1985 Proposal, Nov. 3, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  #2793a
- Annabel Garcia, Bx Lebanon Del., after reinstatement, Sept. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  #2793b
- City Nurses, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  #2794 -- EMPTY
- Bread + Roses Hosp. History Lecture, 10/25/1979 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  #2795
- Hosp. Div. Worker; Joe Campbell becomes U.S. Citizen, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  #2796
- CLUW abortion + working women program, Oct. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  #2797
- Retirees at Walden School, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  #2798a
- Nurses at Beth Israel after Oct. 25 election, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  #2798b
- Connecticut installation, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  #2799
- Pregnant Clerical Worker (10th fl.), Dec. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  #2800
- Bread + Roses History of Hospitals Lecture, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  #2801
- Panel Doctors visit working American Gallery 1199, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  #2802
- Sam Levenson visits JIGC Theatre in Hospitals, Nov. 1979 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  #2803
- CSS election win, 1/1980 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  #2804
- Panel Doctors visit Gallery 1199, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  #2806
- Glorine Williams - Credit Union, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  #2807
- Ossie + Ruby at 1199J Delegates Assembly, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  #2808a
- Ossie + Ruby in NJ (cont'd.), 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  #2808b
- 1199 J Delegate training graduates + Respiratory Therapy class, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  #2809
- 1199 J Xmas Party + Delegates Assembly, 12/1979 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  #2810
- RN Organizers, 12/1979 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  #2811
- Legal Aide Committee Lecture on Utility Consumer Rights, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  #2812
- Presley membership mtg., 1/1980 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  #2813
- Sondra Clark, 1/30/1980 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  #2814
- RN Division Organizes, Feb. 1980 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  #2815
- Beth Israel RNs ratify contract, 2/1980 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  #2816
- Beth Israel RNs, 2/1980 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- Camp meeting - Feb. 1980 (Box 68, Folder 30)
  #2817
- Maggie Hammond, 2/26/1980 (Box 68, Folder 31)
  #2818
- King Center Lobbyists in D.C., 2/1980 (Box 68, Folder 32)
  #2819
- W. Va. - Ky. Delegates conf., 3/1980 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  #2820
- Penn. Prof. Conf. in Gettysburg, 11/1979 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  #2821
- Georgetown Univ. Hosp. Victory, 2/1980 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  #2822
- St. John's Queens bowling team, May 17, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  #2823
- Gary, Ind. "Take Care" performance, 3/1980 (Contacts + Negs returned to Gary) (Box 68, Folder 37)
  #2824 -- EMPTY
- Sophie Gropper, 4/1980 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  #2826
- Greater Harlem grievance, 4/1980 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  #2827
- Beth Israel Patient Care Conference, Mar. 1980 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  #2828
- Beth Israel Patient Care, 3/1980 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  #2829
- Doris Turner - Women's Day, 3/1980 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  #2830
- Swedish Trade Unionists visit, Joint Diseases, 3/1980 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  #2831
- Vieques, 4/1980 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  #2832
- Benefit Fund Classes, April 1980 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  #2833
- Lab Committee Genetic Screening (Richard Sereno), April 1980 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  #2834
- UFT Rep takes Beth Israel RN contract, April 1980 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  #2835
- City Nurses at 1199, March 1980 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  #2836
- City RNs receive CIR endorsement, April 1980 (Box 68, Folder 49)
  #2837
- Robyne Blubes (South Office), 5/1980 (Box 68, Folder 50)
  #2838
- Hispanic Retirees, 5/1980 (Box 68, Folder 51)
  #2839
- Washington Heights Mental Health Strike, May 12th (first day of strike), 5/1980 (Box 68, Folder 52)
  #2840
- Conference on Cardiovascular Disease, 5/10/1980 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  #2841
- Creative Arts Therapists: From an August 1980 story on these 1199ers, 7/1980 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  #2842
- Syosset Hospital: See July, 1980 issue, also August 1980 for details, 6/1980 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  #2844
- Lydia Rodriguez - North Central Bronx, Lab worker, poisoned by chemical (rylene) (Box 68, Folder 56)
  #2845
- University Hospital Strike Vote members, vote to strike see August, 1980 issue (Box 68, Folder 57)
  #2846
- Maternity and Infant Care - Rank and File - July 1980 issue (Box 68, Folder 58)
  #2847
- Long Island College Hospital: Members conduct informational picketry (Box 68, Folder 59)
  #2848
- Flushing Hospital Retirees - Retirees gather at home of 1199ers to discuss action w/Anne Shore/Don Klein of legal staff (Box 68, Folder 60)
  #2849
- Graduation Reception of Training + VP bidding fund (July 17, 1980) (Box 68, Folder 61)
  #2850